

# **CONTACT ME**

**?** Tokyo, Japan

https://github.com/koki0317

koki.webdeveloper@gmail.com

080-7106-9127

https://www.linkedin.com/in/koki-webdeveloper/

# **EDUCATION**

#### Le Wagon Tokyo

Web development

2022/7 - 2022/9

# Tokyo metropolitan college of industrial technology

**Robotics** 

2010/4 - 2015/3

# **SKILLS**

Frontend Backend

HTML & CSS Ruby on Rails

JavaScript SQL

# **LANGUAGES**

Native: Japanese

Advanced: English

Elementary: French

# **Koki** Takahashi

Full Stack developer

# **PROFILE**

I'I'm a full-stack developer originally from Tokyo with a background in mechanical and electrical engineering for three years. I would like to contribute to the company while enhancing my skills by utilizing my spirit of challenge and my willingness to learn every day.

# WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

#### Backend developer

#### Chrysalis | https://www.mychrysalis.me/

Hikikomori is one of the major social problems in Japan. This web application aims to help people gain confidence and leave their homes by completing small tasks on a daily basis.

#### Frontend developer

#### Video game marketplace | https://video-game-928.herokuapp.com/

A marketplace where you can rent or lease a wide variety of video games.

#### Full Stack developer

#### World Breakfast | https://breakfast-alot.herokuapp.com/

An application created in Ruby on rails and Javascript that allows you to browse breakfasts around the world. You can create your own list with images.

#### Frontend developer

#### Sunnyside | https://landing-page-sunnyside.herokuapp.com/

Landing page with cheerful and colorful design, associated with click function to display the modal.

# **WORK EXPERIENCES**

#### Civil engineering

#### Mita I Tokyo

2020/3 - 2020/3

Responsible for site records and drawings. Contributed to the development of new public roads.

#### Logistics

#### Amazon Japan I Tokyo, Japan

2019/11 - 2020/1

As a member of the Logistics department, I was responsible for managing server components and helping server engineers complete tasks in the data center.

# Mechanic

#### Yamazaki Baking Co.,Ltd I Chiba, Japan

2015/3 - 2018/3

I was in charge of repairing, maintaining the product machines, and Installation of new machinery in order to improve the production efficiency.